原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     辰星曉Reginamoon 一了一\ / Lynn_寧
翻譯     胡說大王  八重  咖喱味的虛寒  惠子
翻譯     持久  快用六麥神劍  土方十琦郎
校對     星星與野狗  一美迷妹斯嘉麗
時間軸    噃噃  啾啾啾  紫夏  大蔥浪到分裂  Jessie
后期     8T
總監     somehacker   杏仁斯嘉麗*24
-生日快樂  -生日蛋糕
- Happy Birthday! - Hey, birthday cake!
-我來了  -謝謝
- There I am. - Thank you.
真不錯
That's nice!
這張拍得不錯啊
That's actually a really good one.
有人想吃這個嗎
Wait, anybody wants this?
出于同情邀請人家過來  就會變成這樣
That's what happens when you do a mercy invite.
我覺得你是想邀請所有人
I believed you wanted to invite everyone.
爸  我不能請了藝術課上的每一個人
Dad, I can't invite everyone in my art class
卻不請那個幾乎不與其他人來往的人
except for one person without social networking evidence,
我并不想讓她更加痛苦
inflicting more pain on that person than was intended.
-我又不是什么怪物  -我真為你驕傲
- And I'm not a monster. - I'm proud of you, I think.
她常被留校反省  有時候還會沖老師吼
She gets detention a lot, and she yells at teachers sometimes.
之后有傳言說
Then there was that rumor that went around
她不斷地離家出走
that she just kept running away from home.
也許她可以叫個優步
Maybe she can Uber.
我真覺得我們現在該回家了
I seriously believe that we can go home now.
是我用詞不當讓你們覺得這是民主投票嗎
Did I mistakenly convey this was a democracy?
等有人來接她了  我們再走
We are not going till she gets picked up.
車拋錨了  我坐公交車回去
The car broke down. I'm just gonna take the bus.
你別坐公交車  我開車送你回去
You're not taking a bus, I'll drive you home.
克萊爾幾乎已經攢下了
Claire has almost saved her half of the money
買車需要的一半的錢了  不是嗎
she needs for her car. Isn't that right?
這是最后僅有的幾次
And this will be one of the few times left
我載你們一程的機會了
I can drive you guys around.
我...
I'm...
你之后就再聽不到我爸全程都說著
You won't be able to hear my dad tell jokes that only he thinks
只有他覺得好笑的笑話了  一起來吧
are funny for an entire car ride unless you come.
你不會想錯過的
You don't really wanna miss that.
我收到的禮物比我想得要多
I got more gifts than I thought I did.
我能把這個放這里嗎
Can I put this in here?
當然  我來  謝謝  瑪西亞
Yeah, I'll get it. Thank you, Marcia.
也許他只是喜歡...
Maybe he just is into...
也許他只是安于現狀而已
Maybe he's just content where he... where he is.
要幫忙嗎
Can I help you?
什么
What?
要是他的話  他非常...他真的很有意思
If this is the one, he's so... he's really funny.
-他每周都會錄這種視頻  -這簡直...
- He does these weekly videos. - This is...
-看見沒  -太隨性了  太詭異了
- See? - It's so random. It's so weird.
-你肯定是喜歡上他了  -暫停
- Yeah, you have a crush on him. - Pause it.
我不懂  倒回去
I don't get it. Yeah, go back.
-你怎么會不懂呢  -我就是不懂
- Why don't you get it? - I just don't get it.
他膚白貌美又金發  太可愛了
It's like, he's blond, and he's cute.
不  他的眉毛實在是...
No, his eyebrows are just like...
瞎說  他的眉毛
Shut up. His eyebrows?
-你欣賞不來他的眉毛  -沒錯
- That's the one thing you couldn't get? - Yeah!
但我就是被眉毛撩到了
I get turned on by eyebrows, though.
好吧  太逗了
Okay, that's funny, yeah.
-你看他干了什么  -他怎么能那么做
- You see what he does, though? - How does he even do that?
我給你看視頻就是為了這個
That's the whole point why I'm showing you.
-太贊了  -太厲害了
- It's so genius. - So bad.
抱歉  先生  我想你上錯車了
Pardon me, sir. I think you have the wrong car.
分裂
我們醒來就在這了
We woke up in here.
發生了什么
What the hell is going on?
我們為什么在這里  我爸出什么事了
What are we doing here? What happened to my dad?
他在外面
He's out there.
你知道我爸出什么事了嗎
Do you know what happened to my dad?
我第一個選你
I choose you first.
只要一會兒就好
It's only gonna be a minute.
尿自己身上  尿自己身上
Pee on yourself. Pee on yourself.
不  不
No! No!
不
No!
不要
Don't!
不
No!
把門打開
Open the door!
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
他要我給他跳舞
He wanted me to dance for him.
外面的門鎖上了
The outside door is locked.
一切都沒事
Everything is okay.
我們沒事
We're okay.
我聽見水花輕輕濺起的聲音
I hear the tiniest little splash.
它過來了
And here it comes.
自然界中罕有  就像這樣
A freak of nature, like this.
他穿過小河  他是如此的高
So, he comes across the stream, and he's so tall,
水連他的肚子都淹不到
that the water doesn't even get to his belly.
接著他停下了
Then he stops.
我的心臟都要跳出來了
And my heart's coming out of my chest.
你第一次獵鹿所以緊張了
You got buck fever.
約翰叔叔緊張了
Uncle John's got buck fever.
才不是的  凱茜  你爸是個騙子
That's not true, Casey. Your daddy's a liar.
-那鹿角有多大  -巨大無比
- How big was the rack? - It was huge.
射擊的時候你應該看著哪里  凱茜
Where are you supposed to look when you shoot, Casey?
看著軀干
At the body.
那他為什么卻看著鹿角
Then why was he looking at the rack?
因為他第一次獵鹿緊張了
'Cause he had buck fever.
你說什么她就跟著學什么
She'll say anything you say.
等三年后
You gonna do that
你拿到狩獵許可證  你第一次獵鹿也會緊張嗎
when you get your mentored hunting license in three years?
不會  先生
No, sir.
吃完以后記得把手套戴上
Be sure you put your gloves on after you finish.
在外面手腳是最先挨凍的
Your feet and your hands get cold first out there.
突發新聞  綁架
三名學生被綁架
Three students abducted.
一名學生的父親在普魯士國王商場
The father of one of the students
暈頭轉向地醒來  報道稱他被下了藥
woke up dazed in King of Prussia, reportedly drugged.
他發現孩子和車都已失蹤
He found the kids and the car missing.
有任何線索  請聯系當地警察
鄰居們均表示懷疑
Neighbors are in disbelief.
平素安靜的社區因綁架案而震驚
A normally quiet community is reeling after this abduction.
如果你知道這些女孩的下落
If you any information concerning the whereabouts of these girls
請立即聯系警方
you are urged to contact the police.
巴里
我要見你  急事
你打開那扇門也沒有用  克萊爾
It doesn't matter if you open that door, Claire.
外面還有一扇鎖著的門
There's a second locked door.
他隨時會再進來的
He's gonna come in here again any second,
我們不能再讓他帶走我們中的一個
and we're not letting him take one of us out again.
我們只是掙扎尖叫
We just... we just cried and screamed,
我們沒有傷害他是因為我們怕激怒他
and we didn't hurt him because we were afraid to get him upset.
天哪  都是受害者無能的表現
God, that's victim shit! Jesus!
我們應該跟他打
We should fight him.
我們要對他拳打腳踢
We should drop a crazy-ass bomb on him.
我看見他扛著你們其中一個
I saw him carry one of you and lay you on the bed
毫不費力地放在床上
like you weighed nothing.
他一拳就能把我們打昏
One punch from him would knock one of us out.
我上過六個月的美式空手道課
I took... I took six months of Kenpo karate class.
你弄疼攻擊者來分散他的注意力
And you distract the assailant with pain.
在你們眼中一切都這么容易
Everything is so easy for you guys.
你做一個動作  還能預測到接下來會發生什么
You do one thing, you can predict the next thing.
這種情況下  這辦法行不通的
It's not the way it's gonna be in this situation.
我們逃不出去的
We're not getting out of here!
你的意思是  你不打算全力一搏嗎
You're saying that you're not gonna fight with everything in you?
唯一的機會...
You know, the only chance...
我們唯一的機會
The only chance we have
就是我們三個一起和他拼了
is if all three of us go crazy on this guy.
我們得趕緊行動
We have to hurry.
我們需要你  凱茜
We need you, Casey.
克萊爾很聰明的  我們就聽她的吧
Claire is smart, let's listen to her.
假如你愿意動手  那我也加入
I'll do it if you're gonna do it, too.
-我們能拼得過他  -他會傷害我們
- We can win. - He'll hurt us.
不  你們兩個都閉嘴
No. Shut up, both of you.
你振作一點
You're gonna pick your miserable self up
幫我們逃出這里
and help us get out of here.
你算了吧
Blow me.
你在普魯士國王商場
And your six months of karate
上的六個月的空手道課也算了吧
at the King of Prussia Mall can blow me, too.
不不  你今天不能這樣
No. No, no, you-you can't do this today.
你現在不能這樣
You can't do this right now.
你為什么要這樣  你為什么這副德行
Why do you do this! Why do you act like this?
為什么你一副與你無關的樣子
Why do act like you're not one of us?
凱茜  在瞄準的時候...
When you aiming, Casey...
要把兩只眼睛都睜開
Always keep both eyes open.
用槍管指著你的獵物
Cover your target with the barrel,
然后槍跟著獵物走  掌握它的節奏
then move with it to get its pace.
提醒你  頭幾次會很挫敗
I'm warning you its gonna be frustrating the first times.
你會射不到它或者射太過
You're gonna shoot under it or behind it.
你要學會如何緊跟目標
You'll learn to stay with it.
雌性比雄性要聰明
Females are smarter than the males,
這點你是清楚的  因為就和人類一樣
but you know that, it's like humans.
雌性的嗅覺是保命的關鍵
Females use their nose to stay alive.
確保它們有掩護
They make sure they have cover.
她們總是牢記  自己要努力活下來
They always remember, they're trying to stay alive.
公鹿會發出聲響暴露位置
Bucks go off by themselves.
在交配季節公鹿會變傻
Bucks get dumb during mating season.
男孩子們總是太吵了
Boys make too much noise.
沒錯
Yes, they do.
我比男孩子厲害  是不是
I'm better than a boy, right?
沒錯
Yes, you are.
等你們說的話有意義時  我會出聲的
I'll let you know when I hear something that makes sense.
我們甚至都不清楚  目前這是什么情況
We don't even know what this is yet.
我有了靈感
I... I was inspired.
不不不  那張
N-n-n-no, that one.
粉色帶刺雙排扣長禮服之前那個
That one, before the pink frock coat with the thorns.
那個本來應該弄成...
That's supposed to be like a...
弄成貼身夾克那種
like a tailored jacket,
但我要用手給它印上報紙大字標題
but I'm gonna hand-print it with newspaper headlines.
我是個穿衣簡單的人
Well, I'm a simple blouse-and-skirt person,
但這些...
but these...
這些真是太藝術了  巴里
these are very artistic, Barry.
這正是那種
Just the kind of thing
漢普敦[富人區]的女士們會花一萬五千美元
Hamptons ladies would spend 15,000 dollars on
就為了在慈善晚宴上穿一次的衣服
to wear once at a charity ball.
別說啦
Shut up.
你知道的  我不能待太久
You know, I-I can't stay too long.
我就是來拜訪一下
This is... this is just a... just a visit.
告訴我發生什么事了
Well, tell me what's going on?
什么  你指那封郵件嗎
What? You mean the email?
沒什么特別的
It's just the usual things.
就是感覺有點不堪重負了
Just feelings of being overwhelmed.
你的郵件寫得太簡潔了
Well, the terseness of your email
讓我感覺事情挺緊迫的
made it sound specific and time-related.
你是在找什么嗎
Are... are you looking for something?
-沒有  我只是在...  -沒有嗎
- No. No, I'm just... - No?
只是在欣賞而已
Just admiring.
-我現在好多了  -工作如何
- I'm better now. - How's work?
-棒極了  -我上次和他們談的時候
- It's great! - Well, when I last spoke to them,
他們說你是個模范員工
they believed you were a model employee.
他們覺得你又細致又認真
They found you meticulous and conscientious.
-你知道的吧  -我知道
- You know this, right? - I do.
你已經管理了那地方10年了
You've managed there for ten years.
你盡忠職守  巴里
You're functioning very well, Barry.
對你而言  那里是個難得的好單位
And it's a rare and wonderful place for you to work.
的確如此
Yes, it is.
其他有你這種心理障礙的病人中
You know, of all my other clients with your disorder,
你是工作最穩定的一個
you've been the most consistent at your job.
發生什么事了嗎  巴里
Did something happen, Barry?
你多大年紀了
How old are you?
網上對于這問題的答案不太一致
Just the internet is inconsistent on this point.
你為什么想到問這個
Why is that on your mind?
你退休或者去世之后  誰來照顧我們
Who's gonna look after us when you retire or pass on?
我們將不得不自己照顧自己
You know, we're gonna have to take care of ourselves
別人甚至都不相信我們的存在
and nobody even believes that we exist.
假如我出事了
If ever something were to happen to me,
我安排了
I've made arrangements
巴爾的摩的一名同事接手
with a colleague from Baltimore to take over.
你...你是一個人住嗎
You... you live alone?
你知道的
You know this.
抱歉  我是想問你獨居多久了
I'm sorry, I just meant how long?
一直如此
Always.
那一定很孤獨吧
That must be so lonely.
你猜怎么著  我...我感覺好多了
You know what, I'm.... I'm doing much better.
我不該給你發郵件的
I-I shouldn't have emailed you.
我只是...瞧瞧我  我太沖動了
I'm-I’m just.. Look at me, I'm too impulsive.
順便一問  有人聽你的嗎
By the way, is anybody listening?
有人在乎我們嗎
Does anybody care about us?
有的  實際上巴黎大學
Yes, the University of Paris
還邀請我去做講座呢
has asked me to do a lecture, in fact.
我會用網絡視頻  在這里做講座
I'm going to be doing it via Skype from right here.
人們越來越相信了
People are believing more.
我們下周老時間見
Let's meet at our usual time next week.
我希望你先別走  巴里
I would rather you didn't leave, Barry.
發生什么事了嗎
Did something happen?
別擔心  我只是來看看你
Don't worry, this was just a visit.
我現在感覺好多了
I'm doing much better. I actually...
你的素描不要了嗎  巴里
Don't you want your sketches, Barry?
平時你對它們可是寶貝得很
You're usually very protective of them.
對哦  謝謝
Yeah, thanks.
我們下周老時間見
I'll see you next week at our usual time.
謝謝你為我們抗爭  弗萊徹醫生
Thanks for fighting for us, Dr. Fletcher.
-謝謝你  弗萊徹醫生  -不客氣
- Thanks, Dr. Fletcher. - Welcome.
我覺得我會搞砸的
I just think I'm gonna blow it.
不會的  會順利的
No, you'll be great.
-我們下周見  -好的  謝謝
- I'll see you next week. - Okay, thank you.
我不明白你是怎么和這些人打交道的
I don't know how you work with those people.
-和哪些人  -你的病人們
- What people? - Your patients.
你不能用拇指去轉輪子  傻子
You can't use your thumbs to spin the wheel, dumbasses!
他們總是用拇指
They always use their thumbs.
我們將這些
W-well, we look at people
曾受過重大打擊  與眾不同的人視作有缺陷
who've been shattered and different as less than.
如果他們反而比我們更健全呢
What if... they are more than us?
什么
What?
你相信他們嗎  你的病人
You believe them? Your patients?
就我們兩個人私下說說
You know, just between you and me.
我相信
Yes, I do.
輕輕地撥  輕輕地撥
Flick it! Flick it!
-無意冒犯  我反正不信  -沒關系
- I don't believe it. No offense. - No.
只要您打電話
But when you call,
我們就再免費送您一臺腳輕松
we'll send you a second Easyfeet absolutely free.
腳輕松
只需再多加一點點手續費
Just pay separate processing.
您能得到兩臺腳輕松
So that's two easyfeet...
就那個  我得買那個
That! I need to buy that.
限時優惠不等人
This young offer won't last...
-他回來了  -外面有位女士
- He's back. - There's a lady outside.
丹尼斯  承認你的所作所為吧
Dennis, admit what you've done.
別生氣
Don't get upset.
可別告訴我
Don't tell me.
我有點害怕了
I'm getting frightened.
我還以為你能控制局面
I thought that you had this under control.
-請告訴我為時未晚  -食物準備好了
- Please tell me it's not too late. - The food is waiting.
她在那間房里嗎
Is she in that room?
-我們在這兒  -救救我們
- We are here! - Help us!
我們在這里面
We are in here!
丹尼斯  這什么情況  有多少個人
Dennis, what is this? How many are there?
別別  別進去  別進去
N-n-no... don't go in there! Don't go in there!
別擔心
Don't worry.
我會和他談談
I'll talk to him.
他聽我的話
He listens to me.
他不太舒服
He's not well.
他知道你們來這里的意義
He knows what you're here for.
我不準他碰你們
He's not allowed to touch you.
他知道的
He knows that.
病患編號600-650
-卡倫  -喬
- Karen. - Joe.
他們說你不能在全國學術會上
They said you can't have your own panel
主持研討小組
at the national conference.
不過他們還是妥協了
They conceded, however,
你可以參加情感障礙研討會
that you can be part of the mood disorder panel.
這不是一種情感障礙
It's not a mood disorder.
我知道你的觀念  卡倫
I'm aware your beliefs, Karen.
這次有了新的證據  他們能接受嗎
Well, were they open this time with the new evidence?
你竟然用狗做為證據之一
One of your arguments is a dog?
你竟然提交了一個視頻  其中一條狗
You submitted video of a dog acting differently
在不同的時間對你的一名病人作出不同的反應
to one of your patients at different time?
比那還要更激動人心
It is more dramatic than that.
他們成為了自己認為的人
They are what they believe they are.
他們的大腦學會了自我保護
The brain has learned to defend itself.
你每次提起他們  都把他們說得神乎其神
You speak of them like they're supernaturally gifted.
好像他們擁有超能力之類的
Like... like they have powers or something.
卡倫  他們都是病人  遭受過創傷
Karen, these are patients. They have been through trauma.
或許現在他們能夠做到我們做不到的事情
And perhaps now they're capable of something we're not.
我們現在有腦部掃描技術
We have brain scans now.
分離性身份識別障礙[多重人格]患者
DID patients have changed
利用思想改變了自己的人體化學機能
their body chemistry with their thoughts.
他只是想嚇嚇我們而已
He's just trying to scare us.
他完全可以和自己交流
He was having a full conversation with himself.
"食物準備好了"那句話是什么意思
What was that line about "the food is waiting"?
你們知道的吧  這越來越累人了
Does everyone get how whacked this is
我們得馬上逃出去
and that we need to get out of here now?
你們...  不
You... no.
請保持衛生
Please keep your area neat.
這個衛生間慘不忍睹
The bathroom is unacceptable.
為了便于你們區分
To make it easy,
我用顏色標記了  藍瓶用來擦地板
I-I've color-coded this. Use the blue bottle for the floor.
粉瓶用來擦瓷磚
And the pink bottle for ceramic surfaces.
帕特里夏提醒了我
Patricia has reminded me that...
我被派去抓你們是有原因的
I was sent to get you for a reason.
你們是圣食
That you are sacred food.
我保證不會再打擾你們了
And I promise not to bother you again.
或許他養了條狗之類的
Maybe he has a dog or something.
他會把我們喂給狗吃
Think he's gonna feed us to his dogs?
病患編號617
帕特里夏  11/23
丹尼斯  8/23
病患編號617
黑德維希  9/23
凱茜
Casey.
Casey!
我叫黑德維希  我有紅襪子
My name is Hedwig. I have red socks.
他在行動
He's on the move.
什么
What?
他  在
He's... on...
行  動
the... move.
-誰  -有人要來找你們了
- Who? - Someone's coming for you.
你們可不會樂意他來的
And you're not gonna like it.
你們在睡覺的時候有點吵
You guys make noises in your sleep.
-告訴我們  -我不應該說
- Tell us. - I'm not supposed to say.
但是  他對人們做了一些可怕的事情
But he's done awful things to people.
他也會同樣這么對你們
And he'll do awful things to you.
-我還有藍襪子  -我們是他的食物嗎
- I have blue socks, too. - We're his food?
-你幾歲了  -九歲
- How old are you? - Nine.
所以你不是劫持我們的那個家伙
So you're not the guy that took us?
-不是  -你也不是那位女士
- No. - You're not the lady?
你是瞎了嗎
What are you, blind?
你不知道他們是如何思考的
You don't know how they think?
不知道  他們...他們只告訴我一點點
No, they don't, they don't tell me much.
我剛吃了個熱狗
I just ate a hotdog.
你能幫幫我們嗎  黑德維希
Could you help us, Hedwig?
不能  我...我都不應該出現在這里
No. I'm.... I'm not even supposed to be here.
我把表現機會從丹尼斯先生那兒偷過來
I stole a light from Mr. Dennis,
但他馬上就要回來了
but he'll be back real soon, and...
我不能把表現機會搶過去太久
I can't steal a light for too long
否則他發現了就會生氣之類的
or he'll know and get angry, etc.
-再見啦  -等等
- See ya! - Wait!
我們聽到了些事情
We heard something.
我們之前不明白
We didn't understand it,
但現在知道了
but... now we do.
你知道我們聽到什么了嗎
Do you know what we heard?
你們聽到什么了
What did you hear?
過來
Come here.
我悄悄告訴你
I'll whisper it to you.
那好吧
Okay.
這個人...
This guy...
是沖著你來的
is coming for you.
-你個大騙子  -我從不說謊  黑德維希
- You're a big fibber. - I never lie, Hedwig.
但是  丹尼斯先生...
But -- but Mr. Dennis..
他說他跟蹤了那兩個女孩四天
He said that he followed those two girls for four days
他知道  他要找的就是她們倆
and that he knew that they were the ones that he would want.
你不在的時候
When you're not around,
丹尼斯和那位女士說過了
Dennis and the lady talked about it.
他們說這次他很想找個男孩
They talk about how he wants a boy this time.
他們會把你給他
They're going to give him you.
不  帕特里夏女士  她說...
No, Ms. Patricia, she said...
她說  她不再生我的氣了
She said she's not mad at me anymore.
她有時候還會唱歌給我聽
She sings to me sometimes.
我覺得帕特里夏女士還是有點生你的氣
I think Ms. Patricia's still a little mad at you.
帕特里夏女士覺得我...覺得我很笨
Ms. Patricia thinks I'm... She thinks I'm stupid.
她覺得我會犯一些愚蠢的錯誤
She thinks I make silly mistakes.
看著我
Look at me,
我們就像是你的保姆
we're like your babysitters.
我會讓你看電視  給你做飯
I'll let you watch TV and make you a fun dinner.
我們都得離開這里
We all need to get out of here.
你可以帶我們出去
You could show us the way out.
有人回來之前  我們就已經出去了
We could be gone before anybody gets back, but...
但是我們得快點  黑德維希
we have to hurry, Hedwig.
我們得快點離開這里
We have to hurry and get out of here.
等...等一下
Wait, wait a minute.
在不讓在這工作的麻煩精發現的情況下
It took forever to get this place safe
把這個地方改造得很安全花了很長時間
without the nosey bodies that work here finding out.
你們不能出去
You can't get out of here!
-我得去擤鼻涕了  -不  拜托不要走
- I have to blow my nose. - No, no, wait, please don't go!
誰來了
Who's coming?
-這真的很嚇人  -沒人來
- This is seriously scary. - No one is coming.
他說了點什么
He said something.
他說了什么關于讓這個房間安全的事
He said something about making the room safe.
這都是全新的石膏板
This is all new drywall.
不安全的是什么
What was unsafe?
等一下  確定要這么做嗎
Wait, are we sure about this?
凱茜  你說得對
Casey, you're right.
這里的確有點什么
There's something in here.
他是在掩蓋出去的路
He was covering up a way out.
看到他就告訴我
Tell me if you see him.
凱茜  告訴我們你看到了什么
Casey, tell us what you see!
他來了
He's here.
不能讓他進來
You can't let him in!
別讓他進來  這是我們唯一的機會了
You can't let him in! This is our one chance.
-我們成功不了的  -能成功的
- We're not gonna make it. - Yes, we are!
什么  你們在做什么
What... Hey, what are you guys doing?
好了
Okay, okay, quit it.
別鬧了
Okay, guys?
讓我進去
Let me... can you let me in?
等一下  我們在換衣服
Give us a second, we are changing.
你們在干什么
What are you guys doing?
讓我進去
Let me in!
這一點也不好笑
Guys, you're not being funny.
你們現在的行為太賤了  我要抽你們耳光
You're being bithes. Now, I'm gonna slap you!
我要抽你們...
I'm gonna slap you in your face and your...
求你們幫我拖住他
Just give me as much time as you can.
你們會讓我惹上麻煩的
You're gonna get me into trouble.
伙計們
Guys!
瑪西亞
Marcia.
我還以為我弄丟你了
I thought I lost you.
請你出來  好嗎
Would you... would you step outside, please?
你喜歡嘲笑我們
You like to make fun of us,
但是我們比你想的要強大
but we're more powerful than you think.
出來
Step outside.
請
Please.
你不應該騙小孩
You shouldn't trick children.
那顯示出你是什么樣的人
That shows who you are.
看看你的毛衣  太破了  太臟了
Look at your sweater. It's- it's ruined, it's dirty.
脫下來
Remove it.
我在努力做個好人
I'm trying to be good.
你們不會再看到你們的朋友了
You'll not see your friend again.
她被單獨關起來了
She'll be kept separate.
現在把你們的裙子和上衣脫下來
Now, take off your skirt and take off your shirt.
你們的衣服都沾了灰塵弄臟了
Your clothes, you got all dirty from the dust.
一個分離性身份識別障礙患者的
One identity in an individual
其中一重人格
with dissociative identity disorder
可能有高膽固醇  就那一重人格
can have high cholesterol. One.
有過這樣的案例
There are been cases where one identity
有一重人格對蜂螫過敏
is allergic to bee stings.
其他的人格卻不
The others are not.
存不存在某些時刻
Are there moments where two identities
兩種人格共存
can co-exist at the same time?
的確有時候  兩種人格
There are times when two identities
可以同時獲得表現機會[光]can take the light or the spot,
或稱聚焦  或稱意識
or consciousness at the same time.
這在我研究的一名學生身上出現過
This happened with a student that I was working with.
她的左右手同時
And her left and right hands were taking notes
用不同的筆跡
in different hand-writings
對不同的事情記筆記
about separate things at the same time.
人格之間的差別可能是很大的
The differences in the identities can be dramatic.
就像你我之間
As much as the difference between you and me
會堂里每個人的差別一樣大
and every person in that auditorium.
不同的人格有不同的智商
The identities have different IQs.
有不同的體力
They have different physical strengths.
一種人格是個俄羅斯舉重運動員
One personality is a Russian weightlifter,
能舉起是他自身體重三倍的東西
and can lift three times his body weight.
他們高度集中的能力
Their ability to hyper-focus
和他們不同的經歷令人震驚
and have different experiences is astounding.
這些人是因為他們的苦難
Have these individuals through their suffering
激發了大腦的潛力嗎
unlocked the potential of the brain?
這是通往
Is this the ultimate doorway
所有我們稱之為未知的終極之門嗎
to all things we called unknown?
這是我們超自然意識的來源嗎
Is this where our sense of the supernatural comes from?
是關于色彩濃度
It's about depth and...
和曲線的  你看到那個了嗎
and curves. And, hey, you see that one?
有點像雪尼爾紗針織連衣裙
It's kinda like a chenille sweater-dress.
你是誰
Who are you?
巴里
Barry.
我覺得你不是巴里
I don't think you are.
我開發出了一種"嗅覺"
I've developed a nose for sensing
能夠判斷我在和誰說話  沒有和誰說話
whom I'm talking to and whom I'm not.
是我做了什么嗎
Have I done something?
你已經連續兩天發郵件進行臨時預約了
You've emailed for an unscheduled appointment two days in a row.
我們只是覺得不堪重負  我有一堆問題
We're just feeling overwhelmed, I... garden-variety of issues.
我認為是奧威爾  杰德
I think Orwell, or Jade,
塞繆爾或海因里奇
or Samuel or Heinrich
短暫得到了表現機會并給我發了郵件
had the light for a moment and emailed me.
你卻來這兒告訴我一切都好
And you're here to tell me everything is okay.
是我給你發的郵件
I emailed you.
我能和他們之一談一談嗎
May I talk to one of them, please?
不能
That can't happen.
我告訴他們
I told them
今天我想單獨與你進行心理診療
that I wanna spend the session with you today.
我再問一遍
I'm gonna ask again.
現在和我交談的是誰
To whom am I speaking with now?
弗萊徹醫生  我是巴里
Dr. Fletcher, it's Barry.
并不像巴里  巴里是外向的領導者
It doesn't seem like Barry. Barry is an extroverted leader.
我就是啊
Of course, I am.
我從專業角度猜一下
I'm gonna take a professional guess
根據我從巴里口中得知的
based on the description of all 23 identities
在凱文體內的全部23種人格的描述
that live in Kevin's body that I've gotten from Barry.
我猜你是丹尼斯
I think I'm talking to Dennis.
不過由于某些原因  他被禁止出現
But he's been banned from the light because, among other reasons,
他喜歡看年輕姑娘裸體跳舞
He has a proclivity to watch young girls dance naked,
他自己也知道這樣不對
which he himself knows it's wrong
他自己也做過抗爭  但沒什么成效
and he's fought against it with little success.
我很高興我們終于能見面
I'm encouraged we can finally meet.
我之所以這么猜
And I've guessed this
是因為你進來之后
because you've adjusted the chocolate dish twice
動了兩次巧克力碟子  我知道你有強迫癥
since you came in here and I understand you have OCD.
我知道了  我知道了  聰明
Now I see, now I see. That's clever.
聰明  但我不是丹尼斯
That's clever. But I'm not Dennis.
你和帕特里夏
And you and Patricia
已經有很長一段時間被禁止出現了
have been banned from the light for quite a while now.
最主要的原因應該是你們的信仰
Primarily, shall we say, because of your beliefs.
帕特里夏和丹尼斯很不穩定  我不是丹尼斯
Patricia and Dennis are very unstable. I'm not Dennis.
你們倆現在都是主導嗎
Have you both take in charge now?
請相信我  我是巴里
Please believe me, I'm Barry.
請原諒我  我的職責就是質疑你
You must forgive me, my job is to challenge you.
你現在肯定也知道了  我已經知道了
And as you must know by now, I have plenty of opinions
你們每個人格是如何生活的
about how everyone should live their lives.
問我關于時尚的事  我可以證明的
Ask me something about fashion, I'll prove it.
或者...  你看你看  瑞士蓮巧克力
Or... or I'll... Look, look, look. Lindt.
你看看
Yeah, you look.
你看  我不是丹尼斯
You see, I'm not Dennis.
還要我做別的事嗎
You want me to do something else?
你有冰淇淋嗎  反正這衣服是混棉的
You got ice cream? This shirt is cotton blend anyway,
這領子是三個流行季以前的樣式
and the collar is from three seasons ago.
圍脖領  別逗了
Snood? I mean, come on.
杰  你從哪家"健康"的快餐店
Jai, what health-conscious fast food purveyor
買來這些雞翅
did you originally solicit to buy these chicken wings
還以一種輕微自殺姿態又熱了一遍
you've so lovingly reheated in a minor suicidal gesture?
貓頭鷹餐廳
Hooters.
總不能把它們扔了吧  弗萊徹醫生
And you can't just threw them out, Dr. Fletcher.
這簡直大錯特錯
This is wrong on so many levels.
3點15分的已經看完了  看看3點18分左右的
We finished about 3:15, so look around 3:18.
你肚子上長了肉  杰
You're getting a little soft on the middle, Jai.
快餐店創始人利用我們對脂肪無窮無盡的需求
The authors of Hooters play on our incessant need for fat
還利用了男人總想接近隆過胸的女人的需求
and man's incessant need to be in the proximity of augmented breasts.
這就像亨利五世開了家快餐店一樣
It's like Henry V ran a fast food franchise.
-那家店挺不錯的  弗萊徹醫生  -好吧
- It's a good place, Dr. Fletcher. - Right.
你怎么知道垃圾會灑一地
How'd you know the trash would be spilled?
怎么說呢  杰
How can I say this, Jai.
可能是因為你不夠細心吧
You're not the most meticulous of people.
這人不太不講究啊
This guys isn't very neat, is he?
就這樣穿過了垃圾堆
He walked right through the trash.
的確  任何一個正常人都會繞著走
No, Jai. Any normal person would've walked around it.
這是裝出來的
That was an act.
你想干什么  丹尼斯
What are your up to, Dennis?
還是說做主的是帕特里夏
Or is it Patricia who's deciding things?
我們不會死的
We're not gonna die.
雖然壞事常發生
Bad things happen.
但不會像這樣
But not like this.
凱茜
Casey.
跟我說說話
Talk to me.
我們得找到窗戶或者門什么的嗎
We need to get to a window or a door or something.
不是嗎
Don't you think?
刺激  凱茜  在于你能不能做到
The thrill, Casey, is about whether you can
比這動物更聰明
or can't outsmart this animal.
你之前都不喜歡來這里
See, you didn't used to like to come out here.
這像是我們的家庭傳統一樣  對吧
This is like our family tradition, right?
-這一槍真漂亮  兄弟  -謝謝  約翰
- Good shot, big brother. - Thank you, John.
我給你送飯來了  貪睡鬼
I have your meal, sleepyhead.
吃吧
Eat.
好吃嗎  里面放了辣椒
It's good? It's got paprika in it.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我要把一支很漂亮的花戴在你頭上
I think I'll put a pretty flower in your hair.
好了
Here we are.
這是為了表示你們很重要
That's to show how important you are.
跟我來  我們好好吃一頓飯
Come along. And we'll have a proper meal.
我明白你們對這一切很不滿意
I understand, these must all seem so unsatisfactory for you.
不過我們已經盡力了
But we are doing the best we can.
好吃嗎
Good?
克萊爾能來跟我們一起吃嗎
Can Claire come eat with us?
恐怕不行
No, no, I'm afraid that can't happen.
她差點毀了我們隆重的招待會
She almost ruined our big reception.
我聽說亞洲音樂有助于消化
I've heard that Asian people's music aids digestion.
我再給你們做一個三明治
I'll make you a second sandwich.
你們知不知道
Do you know...
獅子一家一天能吃15千克食物
a family of lions can eat 35 pounds a day?
一頭雄鹿會在繁殖期
A buck can loose 30% of its weight
因為追逐母鹿  體重降低30%
during mating season chasing does round.
它們是晨昏性動物
They're crepuscular, right?
意味著它們在黃昏或破曉間活動  你真聰明
Means they travel around during dusk and dawn. Good for you.
切歪了
It's crooked.
抱歉
I... Forgive me.
我不知道你們知不知道
I don't know if you know,
老虎只有三十顆牙齒
but tigers have only 30 teeth.
比狗還少十二顆
That's 12 less than a dog.
我覺得這很有趣
I thought that was a fun fact.
不
No.
回房間  關上門  快去
Go to your room, shut the door. Do it now.
"日光之下  終現熱忱"
"In the sun, we'll find our passion."
"日光之下  終尋本心"
"In the sun, we will find our purpose."
你一直被悉心保護著  從未真正受過苦
You've always been protected. You've never truly suffered.
這就是我們選擇你的原因
And that's why we chose you.
你一直在熟睡
You've always been asleep.
你從未有過機會
You never had a chance.
那個黑發女孩會被關在另一個
The dark-haired girl, she's gonna be kept in another closet
我...  你可能也知道
I... you might as well know at this point.
野獸...
The beast...
就要來抓你們了  來抓你們三個人
He's coming for you. All three of you,
你們會被分開關著
you're gonna be kept separate.
你衣服上沾了一顆面包屑
You've got... you've got a crumb on your shirt.
請你脫下來
Please take it off.
脫下來吧
Just.. just take it off.
你說了帕特里夏女士的壞話
It wasn't nice what you said about Ms. Patricia.
你撒謊
You lied.
我很抱歉  黑德維希
I'm sorry about that, Hedwig.
你們騙我  讓我害怕之類的
You guys lied to me, made me scare, etc.
丹尼斯先生說你穿了很多衣服
Mr. Dennis, he says you wear a lot of shirts.
我喜歡這件
I like this shirt.
謝謝
Thank you.
你知道丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士是什么人嗎
Do you know who Dennis and Ms. Patricia are?
不知道
No.
你看  我們所有人都要坐在椅子上等待
See, everyone of us has to wait in a chair.
而巴里來決定誰能表現出來
And Barry, he decides who stand in the light.
但是他因為我喪失了這種權力
But Barry lost that power because of me.
我想什么時候表現  就什么時候表現
I can wish myself in the light anytime I want.
這是我的特殊能力
It's a... it's a special power.
只要我想  巴里就不得不在椅子上坐著
Barry just has to keep sitting in his chair, if I want him to.
所以丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士
That's why Dennis and Ms. Patricia
說我可以跟他們一起待著
said I could be with them.
丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士
Dennis and Ms. Patricia,
他們相信野獸的存在  也相信它的能力
they believe in the beast and what he can do.
你見過他嗎
Have you seen him?
野獸
The.. beast?
沒有  我能吻你嗎
No. Can I kiss you?
我想去吻那個黑頭發的女孩子
I wanted to kiss the other girl with the dark hair,
但是她現在有麻煩了
but she's in trouble.
你想嗎
So you want to?
雖然我也不是很擅長親吻
I mean, I don't know much about kissing, though.
好的
Yeah.
太好了
Okay.
好的  開始了
Okay, here we go.
我好緊張
I'm so nervous.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
你現在可能已經懷孕了
You might be pregnant now.
-我的吻技好嗎  -挺好的
- Am I a good kisser? - Yeah.
我喜歡跳舞  你喜歡跳舞嗎
I love dancing. You like dancing?
我喜歡在房間里聽著CD機的音樂跳舞
I like dancing to my CD player in my room.
我最喜歡聽坎耶·維斯特的歌
Kanye West is my main man.
我們在我的房間里放了CD機
We got my CD player set up in my room,
就放在窗戶旁邊
right next to my window.
我就像這樣
I'm like...
"晃動身軀"
"We got the moves!"
或許我可以看著你跳舞
Maybe I could watch you dance
跟你一起聽音樂
and listen to music with you.
-不行  音樂都在我的房間里  -那好吧
- No, my music is in my room. - Oh, right.
你可以偷偷帶我過去
Maybe you could sneak me there.
你是在耍我之類的嗎
Are you trying to trick me, etc?
我會告發你的
I'll tell on you.
-我會告發你的  -我告訴你一些事情
- I'm telling on you! - I'll tell you something.
你可以判斷我是不是在說謊  好嗎
And you can tell me if I'm lying or not, okay?
就像是測試一樣
Like a test, okay?
我故意在學校惹麻煩
I get into trouble at school on purpose.
這樣就可以被留校反省
So I can get sent to detention.
這樣我就能遠離所有人
To get away from everyone.
我就能一個人呆著
So that I can be alone.
好吧  我帶你去看我房間里的東西
Okay, I'll show you something cool in my room.
好的
Okay.
但是要等丹尼斯先生
But after Mr. Dennis
完成典禮的準備工作之后
has finished to getting-ready ritual.
我要走了  他還有個預約
I have to go. He's got an appointment.
我睡著的時候
When I fall sleeping,
他們中總有人想要
one of the others keep trying
去向女醫生告發我們
to reach the doctor lady to tell on us.
卡倫·弗萊徹  心理學碩士
那條褲子  里襯是紅色的
That pant, it's got a red lining.
從褲子側邊的開口就能看出來
You can see it in the long slit down the side.
我們已經談了二十分鐘的絲綢和羊毛混紡了
We've been talking about silk and wool blend for 20 minutes.
我猜  你大半夜給我發郵件
Well, can I guess that you emailed me in the middle of the night,
要求緊急診療
for an emergency session,
應該是有形形色色的問題
due to garden-variety issues?
我不開心  就給你發郵件咯
I was down, and I emailed you.
但是等我醒來的時候  我就好多了
And I woke up and I feel better.
我感覺好多了
I.. I feel better.
我有個想法
I had a thought.
我想談談工作中發生的事
I want to talk about the incident at work.
沒事的  巴里  你很安全
It's okay, Barry. You're safe.
我只是想幫你回憶起一些細節
I just want to bring the details back.
我們只來說說一些細節就好了
We're just talk about the details.
新澤西州卡姆登市的一所高中
A high school from Camden, New Jersey
在你工作的地方舉辦了一次實習考察
was on a field trip at your place of work.
兩個年輕的女生向你走過來
And two young ladies came up to you.
其中一個抓住你的手  放進襯衫里她的胸上
And one took your hand and put it under her shirt on her breast.
另一個也這么做
And the second did the same.
之后她們就跑開了  向她們的朋友們大笑
And then they just run off, laughing to their friends.
你以為她們在玩大冒險的游戲
You surmised that it might be on a dare.
你說過她們大概十七八歲左右
You said they were 17 or 18.
你說因為這件事  你這幾天都很失落
You said it upset you for days.
只是個青少年惡作劇罷了  我現在明白了
It was just a teenage prank. I get that now.
你看  這是我的錯
And see, that's my mistake.
我覺得這件事我處理得太含糊了
I believe that I went over this incident with you too fast.
雖然你說過你沒事
Although you said, you were fine.
而且我見到的其他人格也都說沒事
And the other identities I met with said, it was fine.
但是我相信...
I believe that this...
這件事讓你想起了童年時受虐的回憶
brought up issues from when you were a child and abused.
有時候  另一個虐待事件
Sometimes another incident of abuse
會使被壓抑的人格表現出來
can cause suppressed personalities to take the light.
丹尼斯  如果是你的話
Dennis, if this is you..
我完全理解
I completely understand..
你為什么想掌控身體  保護其他人格
why you felt the need to take over and protect the others.
得了  醫生  你又來了
Please. Doctor, not this again.
其他人告訴我  你和帕特里夏
The others told me that you and Patricia
把野獸的事情告訴了大家
told the group about this beast.
而我告訴他們
And I told them that
這些只是丹尼斯和帕特里夏
these are just scary stories
講給他們聽的恐怖故事  是為了嚇唬他們
that Dennis and Patricia tell the others, to scare them.
這野獸是如何在墻上爬行
How this beast can crawl on walls,
就像最頂尖的攀巖者
like the best rock climbers
利用最微弱的摩擦力和不平整的地方
using this slightest friction and imperfections,
使身體緊貼幾乎垂直的墻面
to hold his body close to seemingly sheer surfaces.
他的皮膚是多么堅硬厚實  就像犀牛的皮
How his skin is thick and tough like the hide of a rhinoceros.
你真的相信這些關于野獸的事嗎
Do you really believe the stories about the beast?
如果你是丹尼斯的話
If this is you, Dennis,
我明白為什么凱文需要你了
I understand why Kevin needs you.
你很強壯  又很自律  一絲不茍
You are strong and disciplined. You are precise.
而且你不會讓別人利用你
And you will not be taken advantage of.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
比如說  我完全可以利用凱文的全名
For example, I do have the ability to use Kevin's full name
把他叫出來  就像之前那樣
and bring him forward, as he has in the past.
但是我不會這么做
But I wouldn't do that.
我知道那會讓你們全亂套的
I know that, that would be chaos for all of you.
大家都會想出現
Everyone would grab the light.
我不想那樣傷害你們
I don't want to hurt any of you that way.
你不需要躲藏
You don't have to hide.
我知道你是在意凱文的
I know you are someone who cares for Kevin.
我并不覺得你邪惡
You are not evil to me.
你是不可或缺的一部分
You were necessary.
丹尼斯  是你嗎
Dennis, is that you?
他們一直把我們大家稱為"群"
They keep calling us "the horde".
就是其他的人格
The others, you know.
帕特里夏女士和我  我們被人嘲笑
Ms. Patricia and I, we're ridiculed.
我們的確不完美
Now, we're not perfect.
但也不該被嘲笑
But we don't deserve to be ridiculed.
我們都在抗爭  他們必須承認這一點
We're all struggling. They have to admit that.
我很高興見到你  丹尼斯
I am pleased to meet you, Dennis.
我也是
You, too.
你好像不知道是誰給我發了緊急診療的郵件
I assume you don't know who emailed me for the emergency session.
肯定是其他某個人格
One of the others.
-現在是你主導嗎  -對  是我們了
- Are you in charge? - Yeah, we've taken charge.
只有我們能保護凱文
We're the only ones who can protect Kevin.
我們都是為了保護凱文
We're all here to protect Kevin.
他太軟弱
He's very weak.
他不知道我們能有多強大
He doesn't know how powerful we can be.
你能告訴我  你什么時候第一次出現
Would you mind telling me when you first came into existence?
還有你和帕特里夏
And how you and Patricia,
那另一個不受歡迎的人格  是如何結盟的
the other undesirable identity, became aligned?
不說也沒關系  你還有堅定的信念嗎
That's okay. Do you still have strong beliefs?
-要看情況  -這個關于野獸的故事
- That depends on what. - This story of the beast.
丹尼斯  有件事也許能讓你不那么迷茫
One thing, Dennis, that may comfort you if you are confused,
你見過其他的人格
is that you've met the other alters.
你們都坐在房間里的椅子上  對嗎
You're all in a room in chairs, right?
沒錯
Yeah.
但你從沒見過野獸
But you never met the beast?
因為他不和你們住在一起嗎
Because he doesn't reside with the rest of you?
因為他住在鐵路場院里
Because he resides in the train yard,
就像故事里說的那樣
as the story goes.
因為凱文的父親是坐火車離開的
Because Kevin's dad left on the train.
但事實是
But the fact is,
你和帕特里夏從沒見過野獸
you and Patricia have never met the beast.
-對吧  -沒有
- Have you? - No.
那是因為他不是一個人格
That's because he's not an alter.
不是第24個
He's not the 24th identity.
他只是你們的幻想
He is a fantasy.
快點  跟我走
Hurry up! Let's go!
過來  是時候了
Come on, it's time!
我知道
I know.
-那是你的CD機  -沒錯
- This is your CD player? - Yeah.
你不喜歡嗎  它有年頭了
You don't like it? It's not new.
不  不  我只是...
No, no, I'm just a..
我不明白  你說它放在窗戶旁邊
I'm confused. You said it was near a window.
在這里
Oh, that's here!
看
Watch.
現在是關上的
Now, it's closed.
打開了
Now, it's open.
關上了
Now, it's closed.
打開了
Now, it's open.
你以為是一扇真的窗戶嗎
Did you think it was a real window?
然后你就能逃走之類的
So you could leave, etc?
幫我逃出去  黑德維希
Help me get out of here, Hedwig.
只要把鑰匙給我就好  讓我出門
Just give me the keys and let me out the door.
求你了
Please.
帕特里夏女士說
Ms. Patricia says that
等野獸來了  就沒人會再嘲笑我了
nobody will make fun of me anymore when the beast comes.
她說所有人都會看到我有多棒
She said that everyone must see how amazing I am.
沒有人會在意我那些愚蠢的錯誤了
And then all of my silly mistakes, they won't matter anymore.
我覺得你應該回你的房間
I think you should go back to your room.
不  等等  求你了
No, wait! Please!
我想聽你的坎耶·韋斯特的專輯
I wanna hear your Kanye West albums!
帶我去你的房間
Show me your room!
就待在這里吧  抱歉我剛才要離開
Let's stay here, I'm sorry I asked to leave.
我不能
I can't.
你說你要給我看一些酷酷的東西  對嗎
You said you wanna show me something cool, right?
-給我看  -我不想
- Show me something! - I don't want to!
求你
Please!
這個
This!
-這很棒  -這不是個玩具
- It's nice. - It's not a toy.
-這是真的嗎  -是的
- This this real? - Yes.
是丹尼斯先生的
It's Mr. Dennis'.
他根本不知道我偷了這個
He doesn't even know I stole it.
很酷吧
Pretty cool, right?
你可以聽到別人說話
You can listen people talking
而他們根本不知道你在偷聽
and they don't even know you're listening.
-用這個可以和誰通話  -別碰那里
- Who does this talk to? - Don't touch that.
我只想看看它能不能用
I just want to see if it works.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
別按那個按鈕  我們會被發現的
Don't touch the buttons. You're gonna get us found out.
這里是東門  什么事
Yeah, east gate here. What up?
別說話
Do not talk.
怎么了
Whaddup?
-你好  -不要
- Hello? - Don't!
我會打你的
I'm gonna slap you!
你是誰
Who is this?
有人在嗎  我叫凱茜·庫克
Hello? Hello, my name is Casey Cooke!
我被關在了一間地下室里
I'm being held in a basement!
我和其他兩個女孩被綁架了
I've been abducted with two other girls!
什么玩意
Who the hell is this?
有人嗎
Hello?
凱茜·庫克  我被綁架了  你得找到我
Casey Cooke! I've been abducted! You need to find me!
貝蒂  是你嗎  這不好玩
Betty, is that you? This isn't fun.
快報警  我肯定離你不遠
Call the police! I must be near you.
我被關在一間像地下室的房間里
I'm being held in a basement or something.
行了  貝蒂  幫我向拉里和魚兒們問好
Okay, Betty, listen. Tell Larry and fish I said hi.
告訴他  他的耳機還在我這兒呢
Tell him I still got his orange earphones and...
我不知道我在哪  這里有個男人
I don't know where I am. There is a man here.
他綁架了我們  他要殺我
He abducted us and he's going to kill me.
我只剩下幾個小時了
I only have a few hours left.
求你
Please.
求你了  來人救救我們
I'm begging you. Somebody save us.
等等  你是誰  怎么得到我們的對講機的
Wait, who is this? And how did you get one of our walkies?
雙手合十  擺成懺悔禮
Put your hands together in contrition.
"日光之下  終現熱忱"
"In the sun, we will find our passion."
"日光之下  終尋本心"
"In the sun, we will find our purpose."
我在超市的慰問卡上看過這些話
I read that on a sympathy card in the supermarket.
是葬禮用的  但我覺得它很好看
It was for funerals, but I saw it was beautiful.
丹尼斯會向你說明今晚的意義
Dennis will explain the meaning of this evening.
野獸是嗅覺靈敏的生物
The beast is a scenting creature,
代表著人類進化的最高形態
who represents the highest form of human's evolution.
他認為普通人類的時代結束了
He believes the time of ordinary humanity is over.
希望這能讓你感到平靜
I hope this makes you feel calm.
你將見到更偉大的存在
You will be in the presents of something greater.
我本來要讓你脫下最后一件上衣  但不會了
I was gonna ask for your last shirt, but I won't.
因為今晚是神圣的
Because tonight is a sacred night.
快結束了
It's almost over.
凱茜  快點
Casey, come on!
我們再來玩動物扮演游戲吧
Let's pretend we're animals again!
快點
Come on!
凱茜  快  這是我們的游戲
Casey, come on! This is our game!
否則我就告訴你爸  說你不乖
Or I'll tell your dad you're not being nice.
快  把衣服脫光
Come on! Take off your stuff.
動物是不穿衣服的
Animals don't wear clothes.
快點
Come on!
快
凱茜寶貝
Casey-bear.
這不好玩
This isn't funny.
上膛了嗎
Is it loaded?
凱茜
Casey?
我是你叔叔
I'm your uncle.
停下  凱茜
Stop it, Casey!
把槍放下
Put that gun down!
我要生氣了
I'm getting upset!
我要發火了
I'm about to get very angry!
把槍給我
Give me the gun!
你差點殺了我
You could've killed me.
收件箱  20封未讀
巴里  我們需要你
-這地方關門了  -沒事的
- This place is closed. - No, it's okay.
-你進不去的  -沒事
- You can't get in. - No, it's okay.
你好  丹尼斯
Hello, Dennis.
你們中的一位剛給我發了郵件
One of the others emailed me just now.
-沒事吧  -我們沒事
- Is everything okay? - We're fine.
丹尼斯  有你是凱文的福氣
Dennis, Kevin is really lucky to have you.
你們很特別  我只是不想你們受傷
You are quite extraordinary. I just don't want you guys get hurt.
你認為我們很特別嗎
You think we're extraordinary?
我喜歡你  丹尼斯  我能進去嗎
I like you, Dennis. May I come in?
我們可以談談嗎
And can we talk?
我知道你想告訴我一些事
I know you want to tell me something.
為什么不告訴我呢
Why don't you just tell me?
我們倆很像
We're very similar, you and I.
都是局外旁觀者
Both on the outside looking in.
請坐
Please, sit.
很少有人來我家做客  我去給你倒點水
I don't get many visitors. I'll get you some water.
他們在南邊那棟樓里給我留了個好地方
They got a proper quarters for me in a building on the south side
但我們都已經搬到這兒了
but we're already here.
他們升我為維修部的主管時
When they promoted me to head of maintenance,
說這里就歸我了
they said I could have it.
你要去見誰
Who are you going to meet?
我想談談
I want to talk about...
凱文
Kevin and...
還有他母親對他做的事
what his mother did to him.
我全記得
I remember it all.
我很高興你突然這么坦白
I'm happy you're suddenly so open.
凱文的媽媽有很多種惡毒的方法
Kevin's mother had rather malevolent ways
來懲罰這個三歲的孩子
of punishing this 3-year-old.
你就是在那時候出現的嗎
Is that when you arrived in the light?
是的
Yeah.
避開她注意的一種方式
The one way to avoid her attention
就是讓一切保持完美無瑕
was to keep everything spotless, everything perfect.
我知道你的出現是好心  丹尼斯
I know you're coming from good intentions, Dennis,
但現在還有其它方式幫助凱文
but there are other ways to help Kevin now.
我的很多病人進了精神病院
I've lost so many patients into the system.
我想讓你知道  丹尼斯
I want you to know, Dennis.
我不會放棄為你們爭取的
I will never stop fighting for you.
我的病人已經成了我的家人
My patients have become my family.
我選擇了他們  而不是更傳統的方式
They are what I've chosen instead of a more traditional path.
我希望你能對我坦白
I hope you feel you can be truly honest with me.
其實我想對你坦白
I actually wanna be honest with you.
我之前撒謊了
I lied before.
你問我有沒有見過野獸的時候
When you asked, if I'd ever met the beast,
我說"沒見過"  那不是真的
I said "no". That really isn't true.
你寫過一個德國女人的事
You wrote about a woman in Germany,
她瞎了十年
who'd been blind for 10 years.
之后被診斷出患了分離性身份識別障礙
And then it was discovered that she had DID.
后來她的三個人格產生了視覺
Then three of her identities developed sight.
你推斷  她的視神經再生
You speculated that her optical nerves regenerated
是因為她的信念
because of her beliefs.
你想說什么
What are you trying to say?
弗萊徹醫生  有些事情
There are things, Dr. Fletcher,
我們都覺得很難相信
that all of us would find hard to believe.
你是想說  還存在第24個人格嗎
Are you trying to tell me there is a 24th identity?
你保護有問題的人
You protect the broken.
你說你認為這個情況很特別時
When you said you saw this situation was extraordinary,
-我就知道  也許你能理解  -理解什么
- I knew you can maybe understand. - Understand what?
野獸
The beast..
是真的
is real.
他剛出現  你說中了一切
He's just emerged. You were right about everything.
他長什么樣
What does he look like?
他的塊頭比我大得多
He is much bigger than I am.
而我是我們中塊頭最大的
And I'm the biggest of all of us.
他很高  很強壯
He's tall, he's very muscular.
他長著長長的鬃毛
He's got a long mane of hair
他的手指是我們的兩倍長
and his fingers are... are twice the length of ours.
他相信我們很特別
He believes we're extraordinary.
相信我們并非錯誤的存在  相信我們的潛能
That we don't represent a mistake, but our potential.
你也是這么說的
You say the same things.
他在行動
He's on the move.
這是什么意思
What does that mean?
我不明白  他不可能是真的
I don't understand. He can't be real.
人類的潛能肯定有其極限
There must be limits to what a human being can become.
這個故事還有另一面  對嗎
And there's another whole part of the story, isn't there?
以不潔年輕人為食
About the eating of the impure young?
"不潔"到底是什么意思
What does "impure" even mean?
我們應該討論這個  你才能完全理解
We should discuss that, so that you can understand fully.
-理解什么  -有時候
- Understand what? - Sometimes...
沒有別的辦法
there's just no other way.
你要去見誰
Who are you going to meet?
他
Him.
你知道嗎  我想把這些都記下來
You know what, I would love to take notes on all of this.
我們應該在明天診療時談談這事
We should probably discuss this in a proper session tomorrow.
真的嗎  你能接受這事
Really? You're okay with this?
這真是太好了  你非常坦誠
This has been so wonderful, you're being so open.
我可以感受到
I can see that you feel very empowered
野獸的理念讓你覺得更強大了
by the philosophies of the beast.
-我... -我現在得走了
- I... - I'm going to go now.
我就知道你會理解的  再見
I knew you'd understand. I'll see ya.
你介意
Would you mind...
我借用一下你的洗手間嗎
if I used your bathroom?
不介意
No.
就在大廳下面  下樓左手邊
It's down the hall, near the stairs on your left.
-怎么樣了  -好的
- How we doing? - Okay.
你是真的嗎
Are you real?
你是誰  救救我
Who is it? Help me.
-救救我  -是有人來了嗎
- Help me. - Is someone there?
-我的天吶  -求你了  救救我
- Oh, my God. - Please, help me!
他們永遠達不到自己的潛力
They will never reach their potential.
他們都不重要
They don't really matter.
聽我說  丹尼斯
Listen to me, Dennis.
我該更仔細地聆聽你的
I should've listened better.
我該知道你能做出什么事來
I should've understood what you're capable of,
你有多強大
how powerful you are.
帕特里夏說你方法行不通
Patricia says your way isn't working.
-世人現在會理解的  -丹尼斯
- The world will understand now. - Dennis,
這真是大錯特錯
this is an egregious wrong.
這些女孩們正在受苦  這是犯罪
These young women are suffering. This is a crime.
我不能讓你把她們關在這兒
I can't let you keep them here.
我們得阻止這一切  這個人格很惡毒
We've got to stop this. This identity is monstrous.
你這樣覺得  我很抱歉
I'm really sad you feel this way.
你不明白嗎
Can't you see?
就是因為你在這里待著  他才形成了
He is formed because of your time in this place.
剛剛有位女士
There's a lady.
有人來了
Someone's here!
我們得逃出去
We need to get out of these rooms!
房間里有什么東西嗎  任何我們能用的東西
Is there anything in the room? Anything that we could use?
什么也沒有
There's nothing in here.
這兒有個鉤子
There is a hanger.
謝謝你  丹尼斯
Thank you, Dennis.
給您  先生
Here you go, sir.
剛才聽起來
It sounded like there were slide bolts
我們門外應該是滑閂
on the outside of our doors.
你試試看能不能通過門的縫隙把鎖打開
See if you can move the lock through the crack in the door.
網絡無法連接
保持冷靜  我們能出去的
Stay calm. We're getting out of here.
我們能找到凱茜
We're gonna get Casey.
你能做到  瑪西亞
You can do this, Marcia.
1  巴里  2  杰德  3  奧威爾
3  奧威爾
印度歷史
就像是卡哈馬那王朝[7世紀-12世紀]被打敗
It's regarded to Chahamana's defeat
以及古爾的穆罕默德從1192到1200年間的征服
and Muhammad of Ghor's conquests between 1192 and 1200.
我想把它比作穆罕穆德厚顏無恥的最后通牒
I would liken it to Muhammad's brazen ultimatum,
普利維拉"要么放棄信仰要么戰斗"
that Prithviraj "either apostatize or fight".
就像普利維拉的反抗
Like Prithviraj's defiance...
面對"群"的進攻  我們應該奮起反抗
we should stand up to the horde's advances.
面對他們的恐嚇戰術  我們應該表現出
In the face of their scare tactics, we should show...
杰德
我恨胰島素注射
I hate my insulin shots.
這里其他人都不需要注射胰島素
No one else around here has to take them.
為什么就我有糖尿病
Why do I have to have diabetes?
所有的醫生  包括弗萊徹醫生
All the doctors, besides Dr. Fletcher,
都說我們就是一個人的不同人格
say that we're the same person, just personalities.
那你怎么解釋只有我需要這破玩意兒
How do you explain I'm the only one that needs this?
你個狗娘養的
You motherfu...
巴里
我穿著九十年代的工裝褲
I'm wearing cargo pants from the 90s.
還有條圍巾
And a scarf.
如果不是里面穿著名設計師的T恤
If it wasn't for the Varvatos T-shirt underneath,
那我就丑死了
I'd be a mess.
我現在一點品味都沒有了
I got no taste for things right now.
我很擔心
I'm worried sick.
我有著失去時間的不祥預感
I have a very bad feeling that I'm losing time.
我能決定誰得到表現機會  不是嗎
I decide who gets the light, right?
有人正趁我不注意  偷走我的表現機會
I think someone is stealing the light from me when I'm not aware.
"群"一直執著于那些沒受過苦的人
The horde keeps obsessing about the ones who haven't suffered.
我不知道他們這樣下去會怎樣
I don't know where they're going with this,
但我感到很害怕
but it scares me.
想象著再過幾個小時你就在家了
Picture yourself in a couple hours at home.
窩在沙發里
On the couch,
穿著你喜歡的那件丑汗衫
in that ugly-ass sweatshirt that you love.
那是只動物
It's an animal.
他叫得好像遇到了土狼之類的似的
He goes like this if there's a coyote or something.
凱文  凱文  凱文
Kev.. Kev.. Kev..
凱文
Kev..
謝謝你
Thank you
一直以來的幫助
for helping us till now.
凱文  凱文
Kev.. Kev..
我想我該告訴弗萊徹醫生
I guess I should tell Dr. Fletcher about this, but...
但她會擔心的  她是個大好人
She'll worry. She is such a sweet woman.
我應該去好好散個步
I believe I will go for a nice walk
系統地想想這件事
and think this through organizationally.
這就是我周一的日記
Thus ends my journal for Monday.
再見
Ciao.
克萊爾
Claire?
瑪西亞
Marcia?
克萊爾  克萊爾我們快走
Claire! Claire, let's go!
凱文·溫德爾·克拉姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb?
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
凱文·溫德爾·克拉姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb!
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
凱文·溫德爾·克拉姆
你闖禍了
You made a mess.
滾出來
Come out here.
凱文·溫德爾·克拉姆  你闖禍了
Kevin Wendell Crumb! You made a mess!
滾出來
Get out there!
你是誰  發生了什么
Who are you? Wha... what's happening?
一些可怕的事情
Something horrible.
我做了什么
What'd I do?
我傷害你了嗎
Did I hurt you?
弗萊徹醫生  弗萊徹醫生
Dr. Fletcher. Dr. Fletcher!
這是誰干的
Who did that?
你干的
You did.
我發誓  我正在公車上
I swear I was on a bus.
之后什么事我都不記得了  我
I don't remember anything after that. I...
現在還是2014年9月18號  是嗎
This is still September 18, 2014, right?
我買了一支獵槍
There's a shotgun I bought.
就在一堆雜物后面最底下的柜子里
It's in the bottom cabinet, hidden behind things.
子彈在供電間里的我的制服柜里
The shells are in my uniform closet, out in the service wall.
殺了我
Kill me.
然后殺了我
Then kill me.
等一下等一下  不要這么做
Wait, wait, wait! No, no, don't do that!
他無法面對現實
He can't handle reality.
我叫杰德
My name is Jade.
弗萊徹醫生收到我們的郵件了嗎
Has Dr. Fletcher been getting our emails?
我們必須要這樣做  我們可以...
This is what we have to do. We can...
在1008年
As in 1008,
喀布爾-夏希王朝歷史
該王朝位于現今阿富汗和巴基斯坦一帶
當安納達佩拉慘遭夏希王朝最毀滅性的戰敗
when Anandapala suffered the shahis' most crushing defeat
而馬哈茂德統治了整個旁遮普
and Mahmud overran the entirety of the Punjab Region,
占領了著名康格拉神廟的時候
taking the famed Temple of Kangra,
我們被"群"錯怪了
we have been wronged by this alliance,
帕特里夏  丹尼斯還有那個男孩
this horde of Patricia, Dennis and the boy.
他們的行為不代表我們
Their actions do not represent us!
他們...
They... are every...
你們大家都冷靜一下
Everybody, just take a minute!
小姑娘...
Baby girl...
他們一直都從我手里偷走表現機會
They've been stealing control of the light from me,
但我們團隊會解決這個問題的
but the group are gonna work through this.
親愛的  我叫巴里
Honey, my name is Barry.
你不該用那個對講機的
You shouldn't have used the walkie-talkies.
他們差點就抓住我們了
They almost caught us.
別這樣  黑德維希
Stop it, Hedwig!
他們說得對
They were right.
看看你  你多害怕我們啊
Look at you! You're so frightened of us.
丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士是因為我才能得到控制權的
Dennis and Ms. Patricia are in charge because of me!
我現在要把表現機會給他們了
I'm gonna give the light to them now.
再沒有人能夠嘲笑我了
No one's allowed to make fun of me anymore!
謝謝你  黑德維希
Thank you, Hedwig.
現在沒事了
Everything's fine now.
凱文·溫德爾·克拉姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
凱文睡著了  我們讓他在很遠處睡著了
Kevin is asleep. We've made him sleep far away.
你想叫他就叫吧  親愛的  但...
You can call his name all you like, dear, but...
他聽不到你說話的
he's not going to hear you.
野獸給我們看了他的夢想
The beast has shared with us his dream
想要有更多人來維持他的存在
of a larger group to sustain him.
不
No!
下一次就用十到二十個沒用的年輕人
Ten to twelve unworthy young next time.
不  不
No, no...
這僅僅是開始
This is just the start!
克拉姆
放開我
Let go!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
救命
Help!
救命  救命  救命
Help! Help! Help!
不
No.
這是家族遺傳的
It runs in our family.
我爸爸也去世了
My daddy died, too.
也是這樣  心臟病發
Same way, heart attack.
不過你不用擔心  我會好好照顧你的
But you don't need to worry. I'm going to take care of you.
你不會給我惹什么麻煩的  對吧
Now, you won't be giving me any trouble, will you?
我知道你不會的  寶貝
I know you won't, sweetie.
我們真是太美了
We are glorious!
我們不再會害怕了
We will no longer be afraid!
只有通過痛苦
Only through pain...
你才能實現自身的偉大
can you achieve your greatness!
純潔者是未被染指
The impure are the untouched,
未受火侵  未被殺害的
the unburned, the unslain!
那些沒受過折磨的人
Those who have not been torn,
自身沒什么意義
have no value in themselves
在這世上也無立足之地
and no place in this world!
他們都睡著了
They are asleep!
你的槍傷不了我
Your gun cannot hurt me.
你看不出來嗎  我不是人類
Can't you see? I am not human.
凱文是個人類  我比他強多了
Kevin is a man. I am much more.
你和其他人不一樣
You... you are different from the rest.
你的心是純潔的
Your heart is pure.
太棒了
Rejoice!
受過傷的人才更高等
The broken are the more evolved!
太棒了
Rejoice!
我的老天爺啊
What in the name of Mary Joseph!
你在這里干什么
What are you doing in this area?
繼續走  寶貝  它們不會傷害你的
Just keep walking, honey. They won't do nothing.
文斯  報警
Vince, call the police!
她說在下面維修區有人受傷了
She said some people got hurt in the area below maintenance.
好了
Okay.
我給你檢查一下
Now, I'm just gonna check you.
黑德維希
第三名死者為卡倫·弗萊徹醫生
Third deceased-- name of Dr. Karen Fletcher.
我們還在聯系她的家人
Still trying to locate the family.
凱茜·庫克斯的監護人到了
Casey Cooke's guardian's here.
你叔叔來了
You uncle's here.
準備好走了嗎
You ready to go?
沒成功
It didn't go through.
我們相信自己是什么就是什么
We are what we believe we are.
天哪  這也太帥了
Holy shit! This is so cool!
現在他們相信我們存在了吧
They're gonna believe we exist now, right?
他們必須得相信
They're gotta have to.
那我們現在該怎么辦
So what are we do now?
我們相信他
We trust in him.
他會保護我們的
He'll protect us.
看看他的能耐
Look at what he can do.
讓他告訴這個世界看看我們能有多強大
Let him show the world how powerful we can be.
分裂
嫌疑兇手  凱文·克拉姆  患有一種
The suspected murderer, Kevin Crumb,
富有爭議的心理疾病  分裂型人格障礙
suffers from the controversial psychological disorder, DID.
現場傳言簡直令人難以置信
The rumors coming out of the scene are almost unbelievable.
人們對于嫌疑人近距離挨了兩槍以后
There are conflicting stories if the suspect is alive or dead
是生是死還不確定
after sustaining two point-blank gunshots.
報道甚至稱  他其中一個人格
Reports even indicate one of his personalities
是一系列動物的混合體
is an amalgam of various animals
就是他工作過的費城動物園里的動物
in the Philadelphia Zoo, where he worked.
媒體已經開始用
The press is already referring
知情者透露的一個暗號
to the alleged attacker by a dark name,
來代指這位受指控的襲擊者
leaked by a source close to the case.
因為他的多重人格
Because of his many personalities,
他被稱為"群"
he is being called "the horde".
這就像那個15年前被關起來的那個奇怪的
This is like that crazy guy in the wheelchair
坐輪椅的人一樣
that they put away 15 years ago.
他們給他也取了個奇怪的名字
And they gave him a funny name, too.
叫什么來著
What was it?
-玻璃先生  -對
- Mr. Glass. - Oh, yeah.